ashemaletube.com 2019-04-03

# Privacy Policy - aShemaletube.com

We, RAZORBLADE LIMITED, the operators of www.ashemaletube.com and all its subdomains (the “Website”), with address at 23 Irodou Attikou, Lakatameia, P.C. 2332, Nicosia, Cyprus and an email address info@razblade.com a company registered and existing under the laws of the Republic of Cyprus, we process any personal data only in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Pursuant to our Terms & Conditions, this Privacy Policy describes how we treat personal information in relation to your use of the Website.

We expressly and strictly limit the use of the Website, only to adults over 18 years of age and/or at the age of majority in the jurisdiction that governs the user’s access (either Guest and/or Registered user) to this Website, whichever is greater. Anyone under this age is strictly forbidden from using the Website.

**_1\. Data Collection and Usage_**  
**Guests** (Non-Registered users) are allowed to, enter the Website and have viewing access to videos, without any registration and/or without the collection and process of any information by the Website.

However, the Guest’s IP address will be recorded and retained by the Website in the event where any misappropriation of information and/or content and/or unlawful act and/or infringement of any applicable law takes place (e.g. uploading of child pornography or copyright infringement).

**Registered members** after completing their account registration, are allowed to view, upload videos and comment on videos and also have access to a number of other features on the Website. During the registration of the new member, the username and email address is required.

The Registered member’s IP address will also be recorded and retained by the Website in the event where any misappropriation of information and/or content and/or unlawful act and/or infringement of any applicable law takes place (e.g. uploading of child pornography or copyright infringement).

Any other personal information such as age and/or birth date and/or relationship status and/or sexual orientation can and may be added on a voluntary basis after the registration process. All this data information with the exception of the email and IP address becomes publicly accessible on the Website.

Financial information (including Personal Information) that Registered Members are providing to us will only be shared with our third party processors in order to initiate and complete any orders placed on your account. All credit card transactions and such are processed with industry standard encryption through third party processors who only use your financial information and Personal Information for that purpose. All financial data and related Personal Information will not be shared by us with third parties except with your authorization or when necessary to carry out all and any transactions requested by Registered Members with the understanding that such transactions may be subject to rules, terms, conditions and policies of a third party. All such information provided to a third party is subject to their terms and conditions.

**Cookies**  
If you have permitted your computer to accept cookies, our Website may use cookies.

Cookies are pieces of information that a Website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make web-surfing easier by saving preferences and browsing patterns, while you are on the Website. Cookies may be used to analyse the Website’s usage and/or improve content and/or customize the Website's content and layout and/or for other customer service purposes.

A cookie may enable us to relate your use of our Website to other information about you, including your personal information. All of these purposes serve to improve and personalize your experience on our Website. Most web browsers can be set to inform you when a cookie has been sent to you and provide you with the opportunity to refuse that cookie. However, refusing a cookie may, in some cases, preclude you from using and/or have negative impact on the display and/or the function of the Website and/or on certain other areas and/or features of the Website.

We use three types of cookies:

a) Session cookies - These are temporary and are deleted as soon as you close your browser. We use session cookies to keep track of you whilst you navigate on the Website.

b) Persistent cookies - These are stored on your computer until they expire and/or until you remove them. For example, a persistent cookie may be used to remember that we have previously asked a Guest and/or a Registered member to complete an online survey. This would prevent you from being asked to complete the same survey every time you visit the site.

c) Flash cookies - If you have Macromedia Flash installed, we may use Flash Objects to recognize your computer for security purposes.

This information is used for internal system administration, in order to help us diagnose problems with our servers and/or administer our services. Such information may also be used to gather demographic information, such as country of origin and Internet Service Provider.

All of these activities, with regard to the Website’s usage information, may be performed on our behalf by our service providers, including, for example, our analytics vendor(s) and our e-mail management partner(s).

**Yandex metrica**  
We use Yandex Metrica to analyse the use of this Website. For your easy reference, Yandex Metrica generates statistical and other information, about the Website’s use, by means of cookies, which are stored on the Guest’s and/or the Registered user’s computer. Consequently, the information generated relating to our Website is used to create reports about the use of our Website. This information is stored by Yandex. Yandex's privacy policy is available at: https://metrica.yandex.com/about/info/privacy-policy.

If you do not want your information to be part of this statistical information gathering, you can disable Yandex through your browser and/or through https://yandex.com/support/metrica/general/opt-out.html.

Please note that our Guests and/or Registered users and/or our clients and /or companies who may choose to advertise on our Website, may also send you cookies. Most browsers allow you to reject all cookies, whilst some browsers allow you to reject just third party cookies. Blocking all cookies will, however, may have a negative impact upon the usage of our Website.

_**2\. Uploaded Content**_  
Any personal information and/or content you voluntarily disclose online, including username, videos, comments and your profile page, becomes publicly available and may be collected and used by other users.

_**3\. Disclosure of Information**_  
We may be required to release certain data to comply with legal obligations or in order to enforce our Terms & Conditions. We may also release certain data to protect the rights and/or property and/or the safety of our Guests and/or of our Registered members and/or of others and/or of our Website.

Although we do not monitor and/or actively seek to identify any illegal material posted and/or any illegal action made through and/or on the Website, we reserve the right to provide the necessary information without notice to the competent authorities (i.e. police and/or other governmental and/or investigation authorities) for the identification of the Guest and/or the Registered member and/or any other individual who acted illegally and/or against the provisions of our Terms & Conditions and Privacy Policy.

If you upload any material which is found to be infringing the intellectual property rights of others, we reserve the right to provide the necessary information to the respective copyright owners when deemed necessary and legally appropriate.

In accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation law in the European Union, effective May 25, 2018, RAZORBLADE shall be in a position, upon your written request, to provide you immediately with a copy of your personal data or in the event you instruct us to delete your data from our records, do so within 24 hours.

_**4\. Changes to our Privacy Policy**_  
We reserve the right to modify and/or revise and/or amend the terms of this Privacy Policy at any time in our sole discretion. You are expected to periodically review the most up-to-date version of this Privacy Policy so you are aware for any modifications and/or revisions and/or amendments.

Although Registered members may be notified for any changes to the Privacy Policy, we do not guarantee such notification.

Any changes take effect immediately upon being posted on the Website. The modified and/or revised and/or amended version supersedes any prior versions of the Privacy Policy upon being posted on the Website.

Upon continuing to use the Website you acknowledge, agree and consent to the updated Privacy Policy.

_**5\. Miscellaneous**_  
If you are a Registered member on the Website, you are responsible for keeping your password confidential. If any unauthorised party gains access to your account on the Website and/or other personal information, we will not be responsible for any damage and/or illegal action and/or illegal and/or other activity that may occur.

While we use commercially reasonable physical, managerial and technical safeguards to secure all sensitive personal information, we bring to your attention that, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure and we cannot ensure and/or guarantee the confidentiality and/or the security of any information and/or content you transmit to us. We do take measures to protect the transmission of all sensitive end-user information, nevertheless, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party ‘hackers’ from illegally obtaining this information. We take all reasonable measures to prevent such breaches of security, but given the resourcefulness of cyber-criminals, we are unable to guarantee that our security is one hundred percent (100%) breach-proof. You assume the risk of such breaches to the extent that they occur despite our reasonable security measures.

This Website shall not be responsible or liable (whether in civil, tort or otherwise), under any circumstances for any amount or kind of loss or damage (including without limitation, any direct, indirect, punitive or consequential loss or damages, or any anticipated loss of profit, loss of profit, loss of opportunity, loss of data, costs and fines and/or any special or incidental damages of any kind) that may result to you or a third party arising from or connected in any way to cyber-attacks, computer viruses, system failures or malfunctions which may occur in connection with your use of the website.

You can access and/or correct and/or delete your information on the Website at any time and if needed you may request us to do so by contacting us at support@ashemaletube.com.

We may keep a record of any correspondence between you and us.

_**6\. Company’s Information**_  
www.ashemaletube.com is operated by RAZORBLADE LIMITED.

RAZORBLADE is a Cyprus registered limited liability company, with its registered office at 23 Irodou Attikou, Lakatameia, P.C. 2332, Nicosia, Cyprus and with registration number HE309571.

VAT number of the RAZORBLADE is 10309571Z.

RAZORBLADE can be contacted at +357 22023053 or by email at info@razblade.com.
